

Applicant for:

Senior/Middle Java Engineer ~Upto 2,000\$

Dr.JOY 5 April 2021

Nguyễn Thành Luân

✓ luannguyen2410@gmail.com

Main interests: Java, JavaScript

What skills, work projects or achievements make you a strong candidate for this position?

i'm Luan, i'm full stack developer, i specialize in efficient java, angular,...i care deeply about building restful api system and web applications.i have more 8 experience years about building from smal system to big system, by apply solution from partners or by myself. i worked bigger system relevant to fitech and banking, current project i works as developer and team leader, i apply this project such as spring, kafka, pl/sql other strong skills

RÉSUMÉ

Intended position: Senior developer, Assistant manager

Bidder's name: InfoplusVN Co., Ltd

Consultant's name: Nguyen Thanh Luan Nationality: Vietnam

Profession: <u>Full-stack developer</u>

Date of birth: <u>October 24, 1990</u>

Employer: Representative Office of InfoplusVN Lucky Holdings Co.,Ltd in Hanoi

Education:

FPT University 2009 - 2013

Major in Software Engineer

Work experience:

Time	Employer	Reference	Position
Currently	InfoplusVN	Lee Yong Seok +84-86-603-3986	Senior FullStack Developer
2019	PayGate	Available upon request	Senior FullStack engineer
2018	KSolution	Available upon request	Senior engineer
2015 - 2017	Blitz Vietnam	Available upon request	Developer
2013-2015	FPT Software	Available upon request	Developer

Commitment to work onsite at Customer for the total duration of the project: 90 %

Intended tasks in the contract:

Specific description of tasks:	Relevant tasks and duties performed previously to prove capability of intended tasks
 Design Analysis Research Coding Unit test Deployment Manager task 	 Over 7 years experience about Fintech projects (payment online, credit loan, real time system), knowledge programming language, OS operation, database structure. Analysis bug and resolve. Communicate to customer to building system, provide solutions. Base experience is software engineer to quickly learn new technology and programming language, working with big customer and partner

	 Analysis requirement to apply technology, frame work support to project, using Agile Scrum to developer project.
--	--

Capacity: project in 5-50 members

1. Credit risk measurement model development and/or validation projects

1.1.Transfer money NAPAS gateway Wooribank 2020-2021

Project Description:	 Building restful API gate way to convert and sending json format from bank system (IBFT) to NAPAS system, purpose rabbits transfer money Building banking business (transfer, investigation, dispute, return, inquiry) Handling Asynchronous api procedure pl/sql to handle data side Webapp component Deploy application to Linux/centos 7 OS
Responsibilities:	Team lead
Programming Languages:	Java, SQL, Maven, Apache tomcat 8, JDK 8, gitLab
Used technologies:	Spring boot, Kafka queue, Angular8, RestFull API, Json, PL/SQL produce, bootstrap
DataBase	Oracle 12c/ Tibero 6

1.2 InfoBox Scrapping 2019-2020

Project Description:	 Building APIs process auto scrapping loan, credit information customer by request to API services. Send SMS automatically Real time push notification Write log Structure database, optimize performance Client uses Angular 8 framework with Coreui by support mobile and PC size.
Responsibilities:	Teamlead

Programming Languages:	Java script, Typescript, ES6, socketIO, SQL, gitHub
Used technologies:	Nodejs express, Angular8, RestFull API, Bootstrap, Material
DataBase	Oracle 12c

1.3.Remittance money, Korea, VietNam 2019

Project Description:	 The system incudes App(Android and IOS) and Backend system Transfer money from foreign countries to Korea Communicate with third partner to valid KYC, recipient transfer money base on policy current country Backend, DataBase was implemented and deployed on Amazon service using docker. Backend use Rest-API, HTTP method to communicate between other side
Responsibilities:	Full-stack Developer
Programming Languages:	Java, SQL, gitHub
Used technologies:	Spring boot, Mybatit J2EE, Rest- API, OAUTH2 Google-Facebook tokenGrandles, Amazon service.
DataBase	MySqI

1.4 Lotte finance, WooriBank Viet Nam, 2018 R-CLIPS/CSS/AML/AFDS(Anti Fraud money Laundering), TensorFlow

Project Description:	 The system is Webapp to identify and show alert if customer profile is fraud in Loan, Credit card productions. Assigning task from admin account to user account Monitoring rule matching, Fraud registration Communicate to other service to receive, transfer data by Webservices The Rule-engine system to handle fraud profile. Using Micro-Service architectures is structure communicate service, with docker compose to deploy. RestfulAPI is present transfer data and HTTP is method. 	
Responsibilities:	Senior Developer, Assistant manager	
Programming Languages:	Java, Typescript, SQL, github	
Used technologies:	Java Spring, Angular 6, J2EE, Microservices, Restful API, JPA/Hibernate, JWT, Aouth2, Eureka server/client, Config serverMaven	
DataBase	Oracle 12c	

1.5 VietinBank, Vietnam, 2018

RLOS-R-CLIPS: Rule credit integrate plan system

Project Description:	 Developing Soap/XML, Restful service, the system calculates base on rule requirement Vietinbank (Loan, Card productions) then response result to RLOS (Retail loan original system) system by Soap/XML, Restful. Analyzing Business requirement Vietibank, working with partners to design Implement rules. Deploying application to Linux server on WAS and Tomcat.
Responsibilities:	Senior Developer, Assistant manager
Programming Languages:	Java, J2EE, Soap/XML
Used technologies:	Restful, Soap/XML, Spring framework, Mybatit, WebShere, Apache Tomcat, Java 8
DataBase	Oracle 12c

1.6 at Vietinbank, Vietnam, Peru, 2017

Customer Experience and Management Solution

Project Description:	 Building system CETM (customer experience and management solution), the system have are two components. First component is ticket system. Second component is web, the system includes functions monitor screen, output report, manage account, branch integrating with other system (SMS sender) 	
Responsibilities:	Senior Full-stack Developer	
Programming Languages:	Java, Typescript, Golang, Json, Bson, NoSQI, Websocket	
Used technologies:	Restful API, JWT, AOUTH2, Websocket, Gox, httpServer, goroutine, Angular 4, SPA, spring framework (boot-security, JPA, Hibernate), Material, Json, Git, Bson, Node npm.	
DataBase	MongoDB	

1.7 SacomBank Ho Chi Minh, *Vietnam*, Viet Nam, 2017 Treasury F-IS Front Arena

	 Building report base on F-IS Global solution (American
	company, top 4 banking software company world), Front
Project	Arena system was built base on C/C++, Python, we have
Description:	worked with vender F-IS to develop report (FX, MM, Loan,
	FI) for SCB, my work include develop report using
	Python language, FSQL base on SQL, monitor system,

	communicate with BA to complete report follow banking business.
Responsibilities:	Senior Full-stack Developer/ team lead
Programming Languages:	SQL, Python
Used technologies:	EMB, Restful Services, Soap/XML, webservice
DataBase	SQL server 2017

1.8 Sate of banking VietNam, Viet Nam, 2016 Commitment report to State of bank Vietnam

Project Description:	 Follow banking Vietnam policy all banks in Vietnam have to commit report to State of bank Vietnam by one system, the system to send and receive report from client bank Report have to follow format from state of bank VN, so validate report is required and execute by the system Integrating to data ware house system Monitoring transaction sending/ receiving report Export report follow State bank of Vietnam 			
Responsibilities:	Senior Developer			
Programming Languages:	Java, JavaScript, SQL			
Used technologies:	Java Spring, AngularJS, J2EE, MessageMQ, Restful API, Mybatit, JWT, Maven, tomcat, java 8			
DataBase	Oracle 11g			

$1.9\ Maritime\ bank,\ PGbank,\ ChinaBank,\ DPL\ Bank\ lao,\ Viet\ Nam,\ Laos\ ,\ 2016\ Anti-Money\ Laundering\ (AML),\ Know\ Your\ Customer\ (KYC),\ Embagor$

Project Description:	 The solution from Tonbeler-Fico Germary The system analysts swift file to show alert money laundering and know your customer, the system includes two part, First component is scoring to analysts file swift(transfer nation money), Second component is web application, Deploying the system, executing ETL from bank database to the system database (KYC). Research issues, writing script to auto run on Linux, develop project to validate file swift from database, monitor Redhat 6, centos 7 Operation 		
Responsibilities:	Senior Full-stack developer		
Programming Languages:	Java, shell script, Jquery, JavaScript, HTML/CSS, Pl/SQI		

Used	Restful API, Websocket, Soap/XML, JWT, Spring boot - mvc -
technologies:	security, Maven, Apache tomcat, Maven 3, Websphere, Java8
DataBase	Oracle 12c

2. Others

2.1 Viettel ITC, Vietnam, 2014-2015

Trouble management system

- Developing web application system to manager trouble of Viettel Group
- The system including manager user level to assign task, the purpose to reduce overload trouble send to manager
- Using Java, J2EE, Hibernate, SQL/HSQL, Struts 2, Jquery, Serverlet, Tomcat, Maven, java 7
- , Oracle 10g

2.2 Viettel ITC, Vietnam, 2013

BankPlus payment online system

- BankPlus is online payment system by mobile network of Viettel, through MB bank gate way to commit exchange money between accounts.
- Java J2EE, USSD, Gateway, Spring, Hibernate, SQL/HSQL, Struts2, HTML/CSS, Jquery, Javascript, Tomcat, Maven, java 7, oracle 10g

Foreign language:

Foreign language	Reading	Writing	Speaking	Listening
English	Proficient	Proficient	Proficient	Proficient

Contact:

Nguyen Thanh Luan/0393251061/luannguyen2410@gmail.com

I hereby declare that the information provided above is truthful to the best of my knowledge and I am legally responsible for such information.

Hanoi, March 29, 2021

Nguyen Thanh Luan